mountainblack.com 2012-03-13

# Privacy policy - MountainBlack.com

Mountainblack.com

At Mountainblack.com, we recognize and value our customers' privacy. As such, Mountainblack.com is committed to ensuring that its customers are informed as to how their personal information will be used and kept secure. 

#### 1\. INFORMATION THAT MOUNTAINBLACK COLLECTS

Mountainblack.com may collect information from you relating to your identity and to your personal preferences as they relate to our products. Personal information we may typically collect includes your name, address, email address, telephone number, IP address and in relation to purchases you may make, your credit card number. Mountainblack.com will endeavor only to collect such information as is necessary for the stated purpose for which Mountainblack.com is collecting the information. For example, if you purchase at  Mountainblack.com, we will require your name and address so that we can send the product to you and your credit card details to obtain payment. Our objective is to inform you before or at the time of collection as to the information we are collecting and the purposes for which we wish to use such information. If we require further information, we will identify the information we wish to collect and the purposes for which such information is being collected. If you choose not to provide required information, Mountainblack.com may not be able to comply with your request or provide certain services. 

There are a number of different ways that Mountainblack.comreceives and collects personal information from you. Ways Mountainblack.com collects personal information from you may include the following: 

#### Communications From You

When you email or write to us you may provide us with your name, contact details, and other personal information in your message. 

#### Customer Support

You may provide us with personal information when you telephone or email us to request technical assistance in respect of our products or to request information that you would like to receive relating to our products. 

#### Email/Direct Mail Campaigns

From time to time we may contact you directly by mail, email or telephone informing you about upgrades, new products, promotions or special offers that may be of interest to you. When responding to one of these campaigns, you may provide us with personal information. 

#### Purchases

If you wish to purchase  products from our eStore or over the telephone we will require sufficient information to complete your purchase your contact details and an address for shipping. 

#### Resumes

We obtain your personal information when you apply and/or submit your resume for an employment opportunity at Mountainblack.com. 

#### Surveys

From time to time we may conduct surveys in respect of our products and services. Participation in our surveys is optional. When you respond to one of our surveys, you may provide us with personal information about you. 

#### Newsletters

We may use your personal information to send you newsletters that provide you with articles and information that we believe may be of interest to you. 

#### Information in Respect of  Products

It is important for us to receive feedback from our customers in respect of our products and any features they would like to see in future products. As such, we may use your personal information to contact you about our products and to inform you of upgrades, promotions and new products that may be of interest to you. 

#### Internal Analysis

We may use the information you provide us with for our own internal statistical and analytical purposes, to evaluate and profile customers including customer preferences and purchasing trends which we may use for marketing purposes and in respect of operations and development. 

#### Updating information

We may contact you to ensure that the information we have in our records is still correct and to add additional information to complete your profile. 

#### 3\. AGGREGATE DATA

Whenever you enter our website or access any on-line information through at Mountainblack.com, our web server automatically collects and aggregates information ("Aggregate Data") in respect of your visit. Aggregate Data may include URLs or domains of referring websites, browser type, operating system, the pages that you access and the date and time of your visit. Aggregate Data collected by Corel is used for statistical and marketing purposes, is collected anonymously, and will not identify you personally. 

We use Aggregate Data to help us improve our understanding of our users and their preferences. We also use it to assist us in arranging relevant advertising, commercial opportunities and competitions. Aggregate Data we collect also helps us to develop our website and audit its use. Furthermore,Mountainblack.commay share Aggregate Data with its co-branding partners in order to improve the content, banners and promotions that you and other users will see on our websites and in our products. 

#### 4\. SHARING OF INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES

We may share the information that you have provided to us with subsidiaries and affiliated companies of Mountainblack.com. Such subsidiaries and affiliated companies will comply with the terms of this policy. 

Mountainblack.com will  share any registered personal information with third parties .If you don't want a sharinf information,please send a email at privacy@mountainblack.com 

As a registered Mountainblack.com customer, you have the opportunity of receiving news and special offers from Mountainblack.com and Mountainblack.com approved third parties. We sometimes share your information with our third party vendors and companies who supply us with support services, on a need to know basis. These companies are not authorized by us to use your information for any purpose other than delivering the services that have been requested by Mountainblack.com. 

In an effort to offer our customers the maximum benefit of CMountainblack.com's strategic and co-branding partnerships, we also undertake co-marketing agreements with third parties who offer similar products or services or who may collect your information, personal or otherwise, in order to provide certain online services to you. 

#### 5\. LEGAL DISCLOSURE 

Although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or other legal process. 

#### 6\. SECURITY

We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information is stored and maintained in a secure environment. We have implemented procedures to ensure that your information is only made available to such designated staff as necessary to carry out the stated purposes that we have communicated to you. 

#### 7\. ENCRYPTION

Orders received by the  eStore (including credit card information) are encrypted using the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) Protocol for browsers that supports 128 bit encryption. This technology ensures that your information is secure as it is sent over the Internet to our server. 

#### 8\. COOKIES

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser of your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. A cookie itself is not designed or intended to read any information from a user's computer (other than the contents of the cookie). A cookie is simply an identifier used by the website that originally placed it on your hard drive. The actual contents of the cookie information can be retrieved by the same server to identify the computer and subsequently to customize, monitor, or regulate the use of a site based on information stored on the host server. 

We may make use of cookies on our website. We use cookies to allow us to automate the access and the data entry functions of our website and to correlate online ordering information for purchases you may make while at the website (if any), tailor our website to your preferences or interests, or customize promotions or marketing. In addition, cookies allow us to track use of our website to determine those areas which are useful or popular and those that are not thereby enabling us to improve and update our website effectively. Advertising partners or other online services partners of Corel may use their own cookies. 

Most web browsers can either alert you to the use of cookies or refuse to accept cookies entirely. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of the website if cookies are disabled. 

For more information on how to disable cookies you should consult the documentation or instructions that accompanied your web browser. 

#### 9\. LINKS

We may offer links from our website to other websites (which may be hosted by our co-branding partners or by unrelated companies) which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and Mountainblack.com makes no representation as to their practices for dealing with your personal information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit. 

#### 10\. CHAT ROOMS AND NEWGROUPS

Mountainblack.com website may have chat rooms, newgroups, blogs, or other forums which permit individuals to interact online. Any information you transmit online in such forums will be made public and Mountainblack.com cannot control nor is it responsible for the use any third parties may make of such information. 

#### 11\. CHILDREN

Mountainblack.com website is a general audience site which is neither designed nor intended to collect personal information from children who are under the age of 13. In order to ensure compliance with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information to this site. We request that parents and guardians supervise their children's online activities. 

#### 12\. ACCESS, MODIFICATION AND ACCURACY OF INFORMATION

We take reasonable steps to ensure that the information that we receive from you is accurate and kept up to date. You have the right to access your personal information, to verify its accuracy, and to correct inaccurate information. 

If you do not want to be contacted for product, service or marketing initiatives, or if you would like to be removed from any direct marketing initiatives, corporate surveys, telemarketing or direct mail or e-mail lists, or if you would otherwise like to limit our use or disclosure of your personal information, please contact us at the e-mail address set forth in Section 17 below. You can also access and correct errors in your personally identifiable information by contacting us at the e-mail address set forth in Section 17 below. 

We will endeavor to deal with all such requests for access and modifications in a timely manner. We will not be able to comply with requests in respect of information that we may have archived as part of our business operations. 

In the event that your product displays dynamic on-line communications (for example, through a message center), and it is not a free, OEM, starter or trial version, you may elect not to receive any in-product communications (e.g. such as product updates) by altering your message preferences in the product. 

Be advised, however, that turning off the message preferences in your product does not mean that you have unsubscribed, de-registered, or removed your personal information from Mountainblack.coms customer database. Alternatively, if you have unsubscribed, de-registered, or removed your personal information from Mountainblack.com's customer database, it does not mean that you have turned off your message preferences in your product. Where permitted, you can only turn off the in-product communications by altering your message preferences in the product. 

#### 13\. RETENTION AND STORAGE OF INFORMATION

We will retain your information for a reasonable amount of time to permit us to use it for the purposes that we have communicated to you. When information is no longer required, we will ensure that all such data is removed from our database. 

We may use the services of third party companies to physically collect, store or remove your information on our behalf. Any such companies will have to comply with the terms of this policy. 

#### 14\. BUSINESS TRANSFERS 

The information that is collected by Mountainblack.com is considered to be an asset. In the event that Mountainblack.com, any affiliated company, division or portions of its assets are acquired by another company, such information may be one of the transferred assets. 

#### 15\. ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS 

By using our services, accessing our website or purchasing our products you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use that are described in this policy. 

#### 16\. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

We are always looking for ways to improve our business and our practices. Consequently, our policies will continue to evolve. As such, Corel reserves the right to alter this privacy policy from time to time. Changes to this policy will be posted to our Mountainblack.com website. We encourage you to visit our privacy page from time to time to view our most current privacy policy. 

#### 17\. CONTACT US

Any requests for access to your information, modification of your information or questions in respect of this policy should be sent to the following email address [privacy@Mountainblack.com](mailto:privacy@Mountainblack.com). 

Last Updated: June 2009
